Wooram Jung

Mid Level iOS Developer, Junior Android Developer, Junior REST API Developer

iOS developer with 4+ years experience and long international background by both working and studying in different cultures. I am currently developing my programming skills while learning Python and Java through the MatchIT program at LTH, Lund University. Hardworking, strong determination.



Personal Info

Address

Bronsgatan 1D, 234 35 Lomma, Sweden

Phone

0793-00 77 67

E-mail

jung.wooram60@gmail.com

Homepage

https://wooramjung.gg

Date of birth

June 05, 1984

Nationality

South Korea

Skills

Objective C

Mid Level

Java

Junior Level

Python

Junior Level

Javascript

Junior Level

Languages

Korean

Mother Tongue

Japanese

Native speaker level

English

Intermediate



Work Experience

May 2013 -Dec 2015

iOS Developer, Co-Founder

TNE Inc (Tokyo, Japan)

- Wireframes and UI design
- Proficient with Objective-C, Cocoa Touch and experience with iOS
- Experience with design patterns such as MVC, Singleton
- Experience with dependency manager tool such as CocoaPods
- Proficient understanding of code versioning tools such as Git.
- Familiarise with 3rd Party API integrations such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Youtube, etc.
- Familiarise with RESTful APIs to connect iOS applications to back-end services
- · Develop custom iOS applications from start to finish

Mar 2012 -May 2013

Junior iOS Developer

Beyond Inc (Tokyo, Japan)

- Create iOS applications based on UI/UX requirements
- Front-end coding, back-end integration and APIs
- Experience with Structured Query Language such as sqlite
- Experience with developing casual game by Cocos2d framework



Education - Higher

May 2019 -Apr 2020

Lund University and LTH

- MatchIT a one year (Lund, Sweden)
- Supplementary programme in computer science and programming
- Includes courses in Python, Java, Databases, Agile Methods
- Introduction to Swedish Culture & Communication

Sep 2018 -

Malmö University

Dec 2018 Interaction Design (Malmö, Sweden)

- · Interaction Design: Methods I
- · Interaction Design: Graphical User Interfaces (Sketching and Analysis, Visual Design)

Apr 2010 -

Japan Electronic College

Mar 2012

Mobile Application Development (Tokyo, Japan)

- · Majored in Department of Mobile Application Technology
- Received Diploma in Mobile Application Technology



Education - Language

Sep 2017 -Jun 2018

Hermods Distance Course

English language course (Lund, Sweden)

- Course: English 6 Passed
- Course: English 5 Passed

Sep 2016 -Dec 2016

Islington Centre for English

English language course (London, U.K)

- Course: General English Super Intensive, with emphasis on IELTS
- Achieved level: Intermediate CEFR B1

Feb 2016 -

Delfin English School

Sep 2016

English language course (London, U.K)

- Course: General English
- Achieved level: From Elementary to Intermediate

Oct 2007 -Mar 2009

Japanese Language School affiliated with Tokyo International University

Japanese language course (Tokyo, Japan)

- Graduated Japanese Language University Preparatory Course (1.5 years)
- Passed Japanese Language Proficiency Test N1